Can I help you?
需要帮忙吗?
Where can I get some medicine for an upset stomach?
我胃不舒服, 哪儿能买到药?
We have some over-the-counter remedies in the hotel shop.
在我们饭店里的商店可以买到非处方药品.
And there's a pharmacy just down the street.
在街上不远处还有一间药房.
OK, Thank you.
OK, 谢谢,
No problem.
不客气.
Excuse me.
打扰一下.
Yes?
Where can I find a doctor?
哪儿可以找到医生?
Is this an emergency?
很紧急吗?
No, no. Nothing to worry about. Much.
No, no. 不着急. 不是非常着急.
Here's our referral list.
这是我们的医生查询目录.
And that's a central number.
还有电话总机号码.
Thanks.
谢谢.
Restrooms?
洗手间在哪儿?
Around the corner, by the phones.
拐角处的电话旁.
Sharon? Hi. It's William.
Sharon? 你好. 我是William.
Where did you send the Engineer Society for lunch?
你把工程师协会(Engineer Society)的人带到哪儿去吃午餐了?
Aha. Maybe we shouldn't recommend it any more.
Aha. 也许今后我们不该再推荐那里了.